(Raj:)Yeah, you didn't have
to buy groceries
because you were breast-feeding.
(Bernadette:)So I guess if it weren't for me,
(Bernadette:)you'd still be living with her, huh?
(Howard:)Not exactly.
(Penny:)What do you mean, not exactly?
(Howard:)Well, things would be
a little different.
Howard, where is my lunch? I'm starving!
(Howard:)I know you're starving.
The neighbors know you're starving.
(Howard:)There's starving people in Africa
who know you're starving!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)That's it?
There's not enough food!
Well, you cleaned out Earth!
I don't know what else to do!
(Bernadette:)How is this any different?
(Howard:)You didn't let me finish.
(Howard:)Here you go, Mother.
You're a good boy, Howard!
Such a good boy!
Walt, did she die
or did you kill her?